M: 0400 762 067 E: alec.bos@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I have 15 years demonstrated experience in analytical problem solving and data analysis, through my work as an electronics technician and as a day trader.

Qualifications snapshop

- Certificate III Electrotechnology Computer Systems
- · Restricted Electrical License
- Konica Minolta Institute of Technology Associate, Professional and Expert (Network)
 Certificate

EXPERIENCE

Sole Trader, 2webs

June 2019 - Present

Day trading diverse stocks and investments through online platforms.

- Daily analysis and tracking of market trends
- Development of forecasts for sectors and individual assets
- Calculation of risk levels and potential margins of error
- Development and writing of custom software to pull trade data from APIs to record transactions
- Importation of trade data into Excel to formulate profit and loss of individual assets
- Calculation of Capital Gains Tax events from trade history
- Worked closely with accountant to determine tax liabilities

Biomedical Equipment Technican, Medical Dental Solutions March 2017 - June 2019

Qualified technician providing support to the medical industry to repair and install equipment.

- Provision of expert technical support and trouble shooting to replace faulty components by researching faults and conducting tests
- Calibration of components to ensure they met code requirements and standards
- · Installation of equipment and accessible training provided to clients and their staff
- Completion of detailed reports and auditing, including state health regulation compliance paperwork, inventory for stock take, registration and lodging of warranty claims
- Worked collaboratively with clients and the MDS team to identify problems, while communicating clearly the process for solving the issues
- Provided a high standard of customer service to clients and other stakeholders including manufacturers
- Self managed work at job sites, to ensure jobs were completed within allocated time assigned
- Provided mentorship and training for new trainees and apprentices

Photocopier Technician Sharp ABT (Gold Coast) Think Office Technology (Townsville)

September 2015 - March 2017 August 2007 - August 2015

Diagnosing and repairing electrotechnical equipment.

- Technical support and problem solving, including performing preventative maintenance, testing machines, installation of photocopiers, assisting with the interoperability of clients software and configuration of devices
- Completion of reports for client history and billing, stock take auditing and lodgement of warranty claims
- Communication with a wide range of stakeholders, including internal team members, clients and manufactures
- Scheduled appointments with clients and provided remote telephone support
- Provided mentorship and training for new trainees and apprentices

ALEC BOSWORTH 2

EDUCATION AND SHORT COURSES

Certificate III Electrotechnology – Computer Systems

Eagle Farm Institute of TAFE 2007 - 2010

Professional and Expert (Network) Certificate

Konica Minolta Institute of Technology 2007 - 2015

CodeAcademy

JavaScript Fundamentals, Node.js, React, Python, HTML, CSS, REST APIs

2019 - 2022

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND STRENGTHS

I am a fast learner, especially when it comes to utilising new technology, processes and software. I have extensive experience in the following areas:

Programming

- Programming languages (Python and JavaScript)
- Front-End Development
- Back-End Development
- Cybersecurity

Data Management

- Advance Microsoft Excel knowledge including formula functions like SUMIF, COUNTIF and Vlookup
- Capturing and recording important data, building charts and graphs, sorting and filtering data
- · Ensuring data integrity

Research

- Data collection
- Analysis of information from different sources

Computer programs and software

- · Abobe Software
- Microsoft Office (Outlook, Word, Excel, Powerpoint)
- Cloud based software including productivity software (Google suite, Zoom, Asana)

REFERENCES

REMOVED FOR PRIVACY

ALEC BOSWORTH 3